我是巴里 艾伦 我是世界上最快的人
My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
当我还是个孩子的时候
When I was a child I saw
我看见我的母亲被某些不可思议的东西杀死了
my mother killed by something impossible.
我的父亲因为谋杀母亲而进了监狱
My father went to prison for her murder.
但后来一场事故让我变得不可思议
Then an accident made me the impossible.
对外界而言 我只是一个平凡的法证科员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但是私下里 我用我的速度来对抗罪恶
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
并找出其他像我一样的人
and find others like me.
总有一天 我会找出杀害我母亲的凶手
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother...
妈妈
Mom!
并为我的父亲洗脱冤屈
And get justice for my father.
我就是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
【闪电侠】前情提要
Previously on The Flash...
你再说一遍你叫什么名字
What did you say your name was again?
-巴里 艾伦 -菲莉西蒂
- Barry Allen. - Felicity.
巴里怎么样了
How's Barry doing?
- 这是个秘密 - 哪种秘密
- It's a secret. - What kind of secret?
我必须保守的秘密
The kind I have to keep.
我有过一点点经验
I just have a little experience
喜欢一个以不同的方式看待你的人
with liking someone who doesn't see the same way.
- 爸爸 事情就是 - 你们俩在一起
- Dad, the thing is... - You two are dating.
- 所以你没气疯 - 噢 我气疯了
- So you're not mad. - Oh, I'm mad.
世界上最快的人下班之后会做什么呢
What does the fastest man alive do on his day off?
在被闪电劈中之前 我不是呆在犯罪实验室
Before the lightning bolt, if I wasn't still at the crime lab,
就是宅在家里无所事事
I'd be at home chilling,
但是现在不同了
but now my days off are different.
现在他们都不会那么孤单了
Now they aren't so lonely.
闪电不仅仅给了我速度
The lightning didn't just give me speed.
也给了我朋友
It also gave me friends.
这个在结构上错得太离谱了
This isn't even remotely anatomically correct.
那不是重点 斯诺博士
That's not the point, Dr. Snow.
那什么是重点
Then what is the point?
好玩啊
To have fun.
还有通过同时完成多项任务的方式
And to continue your ongoing training by testing the speed
测试你的思维速度来对你进行继续训练
of your mind by pushing your ability to multitask.
我在等你呢 韦尔斯博士
I'm waiting on you, Dr. Wells.
182秒 先生们
182 seconds, gentlemen.
当心点 我想我们遇到麻烦了
Heads up! I think we got something.
2-11 2-11 有人抢劫
2-11, 2-11. We're being robbed!
嘿 冷静点
Hey, cool it.
还有158秒
158 seconds to go.
将军
Checkmate.
- 等等 将军吗 - 将军
- Wait, checkmate? - Checkmate.
我想你还得学着点
I guess we still have a few things left to learn,
不是吗 艾伦先生
don't we, Mr. Allen?
第四大道和柯林斯街交界处发生持械抢劫
Armed robbery at 4th and Collins.
郑重声明 操作能力和乒乓球我可都赢了
For the record, I crushed it in operation and ping pong.
这个并不像看起来那么容易
It's not as easy as it looks.
啊
Ugh!
最近的医院在哪儿
Where's the nearest hospital?
圣安德鲁斯医院 先往北过七个街区 再往东过两个
St. Andrews... Seven blocks north, two east.
给急诊室打个电话 告诉他们将有一个枪弹伤者被送过去
Call the ER, tell them they have an incoming GSW.
快去 我要把这整个街区
Let's go. I want this locked up all the way
都封锁起来
to the end of the block.
两辆卡车被偷了
Tow truck was stolen.
装甲车的驾驶员现在在圣安德鲁斯医院
Driver of the armored car is in a stable condition
情况稳定 但是没人知道他是怎么到那儿去的
at St. Andrews, and no one's exactly sure how he got there.
你有没有查看监控录像
Did you check the security cameras?
摄像机的存储驱动器被偷了
Camera's storage drive was stolen.
这些家伙挺专业啊
Guys are pros.
所有东西都还在这儿
Everything's still here,
包括我以为他们要抢的
including what I think they were after,
康达克王朝钻石
the Kahndaq dynasty diamond.
它正在送往中城博物馆展览的途中
It was on its way to central city museum for exhibition.
对 艾瑞斯还想让我去博物馆
Right, Iris is trying to talk me into going.
我对博物馆的兴趣不大
I'm not much of a museum guy,
但是当她真心想要干嘛的时候
but when she really wants to do something...
我先走了
I'm just going to walk away now.
对不起 长官 我刚刚去医院
Sorry, captain. I was at the hospital
- 看望一个朋友 - 没丢什么东西
- visiting a friend. - There's nothing missing.
看起来像是有人阻止了一场抢劫
It looks like someone interrupted a robbery.
守卫说他们有三个人
Guard says there was three of them.
事实上 有四个
Actually, there was four.
我是说 如果去我抢劫这类型的
I mean, that's how many I would bring
我会带这么多人
if I were doing a robbery of this nature.
那确实是一辆坐着四人的卡车
That's definitely a four guy truck.
一个驾驶员 两个人对付守卫 还有
A driver, two more to cover the guards, and...
一个人用液氮来破门
Somebody used liquid nitrogen to crack open this door,
所以是四个坏蛋
so four bad guys.
谢谢你 艾伦先生 你如此牛逼的洞察力
Thank you, Mr. Allen, for your brilliant insight.
作为一个如此快的人
For somebody so fast,
你在编故事这方面反应有点慢啊
you're a little slow on the improvising.
你发现了什么可以帮助我们抓住这些家伙的东西吗
Did you see anything that could help us catch these guys?
是的 他们其中一人丢失了面罩
Yeah, one of them lost his mask.
我看见了他的脸
I saw his face.
看看这些中城头号通缉犯的照片
So look through these mug shots of Central City's most wanted,
看能不能找到我们要找的家伙
and see if you can find our guy.
是他
That's him.
妈的
Damn.
莱昂纳多·史纳特
Leonard Snart.
莱昂纳多 名字差不多跟巴塞洛缪一样难听
Leonard? That's almost as bad as Bartholomew.
史纳特也不好听啊
Snart ain't sexy, either.
史纳特的父亲是个警察
Snart's father was a cop...
是个坏警察
Was a bad cop.
他总是拿他的孩子出气 直到他最终进了监狱
Took his anger out on his kids until he went to prison.
史纳特的父亲也在监狱里
Snart's dad's in prison too?
我们可以开个俱乐部了
We should start a club.
他 大概 每半年出现一次
He shows up, like, every six months.
他在行动之前会勘察好几周
He cases a job for weeks before he makes his move.
然后就作案 逃跑
Then, he does the job... Gets away.
那是在红色印迹出现之前
That's before The Streak was around.
你刚刚是用第三人称称呼你自己吗
Did you just refer to yourself in the third person?
我是说红色印迹 而且我可以超越它
I referred to The Streak, which I'm pretty sure I can top.
我一直在想新的名字
I've been thinking of a new name.
你觉得闪电
What do you think about The Fla...
咖啡时间
Coffee break.
我要把中城里最好喝的爪哇咖啡
Thought I would bring Central City's finest java
带给中城最棒的人喝
over to Central City's finest.
谢谢 我戒咖啡因了
Thanks. I'm off caffeine.
自从我把我跟埃迪的事告诉我爸之后
My dad's been mad at me every since I told him
他就一直在生我的气
about me and Eddie.
不 我觉得他生气是因为你没告诉他
No, you mean he's mad at you because you didn't tell him.
呃 首先 这话听起来 你是站在他那边的
Uh, first, that sounds like you're taking his side,
第二 你知道他是怎么对待这一切的吗
and second, do you know how he does this whole,
我不会跟你说话 但是从此以后
I'm not talking to you, but I have a whole bag
我会用批判的眼光看到你们
"Full of judgmental looks I'm gonna try out on you later?
嗯 我也有几次
yeah, I've been on the receiving end
这样的经历
of those a few times.
说到交流
Speaking of communications,
或者缺少理论 上完这么多新闻课之后
or lack thereof, after all of these journalism classes,
-我想到了个主意 -嗯
- I got an idea. - Huh.
我开了个博客
I started a blog.
哦 关于什么的 你的布朗尼痴迷症吗
All right, what's it about? Your brownie obsession?
因为 你知道的 有些东西不说出去比较好
'Cause, you know, you probably shouldn't broadcast that.
不 是一些重要事情
No, something important.
中城市民需要知道的事情 就是那道红色印迹
Something that Central City needs to know about, The Streak.
他真的存在 巴里
He's out there, Barry.
有人说 他阻止了早先那场装甲车抢劫案
Rumor has it, he stopped an armed car robbery earlier.
我希望能够看看相关文件 并且
I was hoping that I could take a look at the file, and...
什么  我不能随意
What? I'm not at liberty
跟你讨论一桩正在调查中的案子
to discuss an ongoing police investigation with you.
从什么时候开始的 大嘴巴先生
Since when, Mr. Blabbermouth?
相信一个自11岁开始就一直
Take it from someone who's been
在调查一件不可思议案件的人吧
investigating the impossible since they were 11.
写这方面的博客
Blogging about this is
你只会搬石头砸自己的脚
only gonna bring the crazies to your front door.
我的博客是匿名的
My blog is anonymous.
无论是否署名 都是不安全的
All right, well, anonymous or not, it's not safe.
你永远都不会知道在网上四处闲逛的
You never know what kind of weirdos are out there
都有什么样的怪胎
trolling on the internet.
我能担保那是真的
I can vouch for that.
网上到处都是奇葩和激进分子
The internet is full of weirdos and nerd rage...
无数无数的愤青
Lots and lots of nerd rage.
你好 我是菲莉西蒂·斯莫克
Hi. Felicity Smoak.
我是艾瑞斯·韦斯特
Iris West.
我是巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
不过你们都已经知道了 菲莉西蒂是…
But you both already knew that. Felicity is...
你在星城认识的
The girl that you met in Starling City,
电脑专家 是吧
the computerer, right?
你们一起研究巴里的一个不可解释案件
You two worked on one of Barry's unexplainable cases.
长话短说 其实真的是可以合理解释的一个案子
Which, long story short, was definitely explainable.
所以闪电侠来这里了是吗
So the lightning came through here?
是的
Yeah.
过去几周就已经有些谣言了
There's been some rumors the last few weeks.
人们在街上看到了一个红色模糊的身影
People seen a red blur tearing through the streets.
那究竟是什么
What the hell is it, man?
那可能是个无人机
Maybe it was a drone.
顶尖的军事机密
Some top secret army thing.
在我小时候 我祖父常常
When I was a kid, my grandfather used to
带我和我姐姐去汽车餐厅吃饭
take my sister and me to this diner, the motorcar.
食物很难吃 但是卖相却很好
Food was for crap, but the view was great,
就在中城警署对面
right across from the Central City precinct.
我现在还是会去那里 去听听他们的广播
I still go there. I listen to their radios.
弄懂他们的反应时间
I learn their response times.
城中心有40家银行
There are 40 banks in Central City,
每家银行都会在60秒内得到警察的支援
each of them within 60 seconds of police response.
这也是瞄准移动目标的好处
That's the advantage of hitting a moving target.
当装甲车报警时
Once the armored car called 911,
在警察赶到之前 我们还有182秒的时间可以逃离
we had 182 seconds before any cop could be on the scene.
没有人能够及时阻止我们
No one could have gotten there fast enough to stop us.
但是有东西出阻止了
But something did,
然后你就乱了阵脚
and you lost your cool.
你知道规矩的
You know the rules.
不在万不得已的时候 我们绝不击毙警卫或者警察
We don't shoot guards or cops unless it's the only option.
我们不需要这个高潮
We don't need the heat.
高潮?
The heat?
你觉得那团模糊是什么 史纳特
What the hell do you think the blur is, Snart?
算了 去他妈的
Right. Screw this.
去你的 我不干了
Screw you. I'm out.
你不干了 那你也就没什么用处了
Well, if you're out, you're out.
那团模糊是个人
This blur is a man.
看来游戏得升级了
We're gonna have to up our game.
艾瑞斯人很好
Iris seems very nice.
也很漂亮  超级美
And really pretty. Like, super pretty.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
但她不是我女朋友
Well, Iris isn't my girlfriend.
其实她已经名花有主了
She's just a friend who actually has a boyfriend.
噢 那还 真是有意思
Oh, that's... Interesting,
我猜
I guess.
你来这里干嘛
What are you really doing here?
我是高兴见到你
I mean, it's good to see you,
但你和奥利弗是不是有什么需要…
but do you and Oliver need something, or...
不不 我是来是因为我想见你
No, no, I came because I wanted to see you.
我听说你从昏迷中醒来
I heard you were out of the coma.
没给我打电话 没有写信给我
Didn't call, didn't write,
也没有跑过来
didn't race over...
奥利弗告诉你的吗
Oliver told you?
其实 那天晚上我听到
Honestly, I heard you two talking
你们两个在星城楼顶的谈话
on that rooftop in Starling City that night.
我想看看
I want to see it.
我是指你的速度
And by I mean your speed,
别以为我是在说其他的什么
in case you thought I was talking about something else,
-我别无他意 -好
- which I... which I was not. - Okay.
你看到那座楼了吗
Okay, you see that building?
嗯
Uh-huh.
睁大眼睛看着它
Keep your eyes on it.
呜 呼
Whoo-hoo!
哇哦
Whoa.
你给我拍了张照
You took a picture of me?
从那座楼顶上吗
From the top of that building?
是的 不要分享那个照片
Yeah. Don't instagram that.
不可思议
Unbelievable.
你的鞋子在冒烟
Your shoes are smoking.
没 没事 这个 这个 偶尔会发生
That... that's fine. It's... it happens sometimes.
这也是我会有一套防摩擦制服的原因
It's why I have a friction-proof suit.
你从哪得到的
Where did you get that?
我带你去看
I'll show you.
闪电侠
第一季 第四集
这是我的团队
And this is where my team
模拟警用波频监控犯罪活动的地方
monitors the police bands for criminal activity.
我们能追踪到这个城市里发生的任何事情
We can track anything that's happening in the city.
来看看这个
Check this out.
我们有自己的人造卫星
We've got our own satellite.
我知道
I know.
我偶尔会黑进去
I've hacked into it from time to time.
-真没礼貌 -是的 没错
- Rude. - It is, of course,
能再看到你太好了 菲莉西蒂
so wonderful to see you again, Felicity.
我只是想知道
I'm just wondering
她还需要知道多少我们的行动
how much of our operation she needs to know about.
我真的很善于保守秘密
I'm really good at keeping secrets.
对了 菲莉西蒂和绿箭侠一起工作
Yeah, Felicity works with The Arrow.
-酷毙了 -而你很显然没有和他们一起
- Sweet. - And you apparently are not.
现在一切都说得通了
Now it's all making sense.
你知道谁是绿箭侠吗
You know who The Arrow is.
等下  你知道谁是绿箭侠吗
Wait, do you know who The Arrow is?
嗯
Uh...
只能说我的队伍有一个类似的配置
Let's just say that my team has a similar set up,
但有 我们的目标更有针对性
but with... More pointy objects.
欢迎 斯莫克小姐
Welcome, Ms. Smoak.
韦尔斯博士
Dr. Wells?
传说中的韦尔斯博士吗
The Dr. Wells?
叫我哈里森就可以了 菲莉西蒂
Please, call me Harrison, Felicity.
你知道我是谁
Oh, you know who I am?
19岁就在
Ranked second in
国家信息技术竞赛中
the national informative technology competition
取得第二名的佳绩
at age 19,
毕业于麻省理工 取得
graduated M.I.T. With masters degree
网络安全和计算机科学专业的硕士学位
in cyber security and computer sciences.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我一直关注科学领域有潜力的天才
I keep an eye out for promising talent in scientific fields.
就是这样找到了思科 凯特琳
It's what brought me Cisco, Caitlin,
我在你身上看到了无限的潜能
and I foresaw great things from you.
说到潜能
Speaking of great things,
想看一些很酷的东西吗
want to see something cool?
他能跑多快
How fast can he run?
理论上来说
He hasn't reached his top speed yet,
他还没有达到他的最快速度
theoretically speaking.
他真的没有问题吗
So is he really okay?
他的心跳对他来说是在正常范围内
His heart rate is within normal range for him.
不 我的意思是 闪电球改变了他
No, I mean, the lightning bolt changed him.
你们中有人知道 改变了多少吗
Do any of you really know how much?
我们知道的相当多
We know a fair amount.
如果他身上的一切都在加速
If everything about him is sped up,
他是否会老的更快
is he going to age faster?
如果他跑得太快了会怎样
What would happen if he ran too fast?
我是说 他会不会跑着跑着 然后 噗
I mean, would he just be running, and then, poof,
他就在红衣里面化成一堆灰
he's dust in a red costume?
我们在科技之星实验室里做的一切
Everything we do here at S.T.A.R. Labs
都是为了保护巴里·艾伦
is to protect Barry Allen.
相信我 菲莉西蒂 他在这里被照顾得很好
Trust us, Felicity, he is in very good hands here.
想知道我倒退能跑多快吗
Want to see how fast I can run backwards?
别担心 他痊愈也很快
Don't worry. He heals quickly too.
嗯 我不明白
Eh, I don't get it.
史纳特为什么要来这里
Why would snart come here?
史纳特之前也被制止过
Snart's been deterred before,
但一旦他想要得到什么东西
but once he goes after something,
他不达目的决不罢休的
he doesn't stop until he gets it, ever.
乔 我要你知道我对艾瑞斯是认真的
Joe, I want you to know that I'm really serious about Iris.
她是个了不起的女人 我真的能看到我自己
She's an amazing woman, and I can really see myself...
我跟你说过我大学最后一天
I ever tell you about that wild night
那个荒唐的晚上吗
I had my last day of college?
我想没有 没有吧
I don't think so. No?
我们下班后也没一起出去喝点啤酒吗
Not even after we kicked back a few beers after work?
我们从来没有
We've never done that.
哦 是的
Oh, right.
那是我和我朋友才一起做的事
That's the things I do with my friends,
既然我们从没那样过 我们就不是朋友
and since we've never done those things we ain't friends.
所有实际上 我没有任何理由
So there's actually no reason
需要知道你约会的事
I need to know about your dating life.
我只是不希望我和你女儿的
I just don't want my personal relationship
私人关系影响到我们的工作关系
with your daughter to affect our working relationship.
这不关你的事 埃迪 是艾瑞斯
It ain't about you, Eddie. It's about her.
那只要我们不谈论你和她的事
So as long as we don't talk about you and her,
我俩就没事
we will be cool.
我们听听广播好了
Maybe we should just listen to the radio.
当一个男人爱上一个女人
When a man loves a woman
我们开始吧
let's get it on
还是安静呆着吧
Quiet is good.
-谢谢你 -好的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
嗨 你们两个
Hey, you two.
- 嗨 - 我们俩不是俩
- Hey. - We're not a two.
哦 是的 我是我 他是他
Oh, no. We are a one and one.
对的
Yeah.
巴里有没有带你去
Has Barry been showing you
看看中城的美景呢
some of the sights in Central City?
有的 我看到了不少奇妙的事儿
Yes, I have seen some pretty amazing things.
是嘛
Really?
好吧 如果你还有时间的话
Well, if you've got some time,
或者我们可以带你去见识见识中城的夜生活
maybe we can show you some of Central City's night life.
噢 算了啦
Oh, no.
星城的夜生活超丰富 我已经受够了
I get plenty of night life in Starling City.
噢 我要带你去玩儿的东西
Oh, this is something that
你肯定不想错过
I don't think that you're gonna want to miss.
游戏厅的益智问答比赛
Trivia night at Jitters.
我承认艾迪可能不怎么感兴趣
Eddie's not really excited about it, I admit.
不过肯定会是超级棒的一晚上的 伙计们
But it could be our night, guys.
玩一晚上益智问答 就为了赢几杯75美元的卡布奇诺
Our night to win $75 worth of cappuccinos.
额 可美味啦
Uh, yum.
内什么 我先去安排一下工作的事儿
You know what, I'm gonna go call work,
向领导报个到 看看还有啥问题
check in, make sure everything's okay.
马上回来哦
I'll be back in a second.
- 你为什么要这样 - 怎么样
- Why are you doing this? - Doing what?
和你还有艾迪 玩益智问答游戏
The trivia night with you and Eddie,
极力安排这样的四人约会
forcing this whole double date thing.
因为这姑娘很棒
Because that girl is great,
而且正好和你这种呆瓜能聊到一块
and she happens to come from your very rare species
这可不容易啊
of adorable nerds.
你再跟我说说她的事儿呗
Why didn't you tell me more about her?
没啥好说的啊
There's nothing to tell.
她只是个普通朋友
She's just a friend.
巴里 姑娘们不会就这么跳上辆火车
Barry, girls don't just hop on trains
然后不远万里
and travel hundreds of miles
去见一个她不喜欢的人
to see someone that they don't like.
你看 这种时候 就需要我出马了
See, this is why you need my help.
今晚把她带上
Bring her tonight.
我们一起开心开心
We'll have fun.
呵呵 开心
Yeah, fun.
你说要最高端的货 斯奈特
You wanted state of the art, Snart.
我就给你搞来了最高端的 我的好先生
I bring you state of the art, my good sir.
- 这是神马 - 这货可能看上去平平无奇
- What's this? - It might not look like much,
不过千万不要以貌取物 你懂的
but never judge a book by its cover, you know?
火焰高度聚集 液体燃料
Fires highly concentrated, combustible liquid fuel
和空气一触即燃
that ignites on contact with the air.
我不需要让东西烧起来
I don't need to heat things up.
我要让他们慢下去
I need to slow them down.
那就是它了
That's the one, then.
就是这个箱子里的货
You were drawn right to it.
那场事故之后 从科技之星实验室偷出来的
Stolen from S.T.A.R. Labs after the incident,
当时守卫它的警卫
and with nothing but a skeleton security crew
只剩下一堆白骨了
to guard the tech inside.
能发射出某种物质 我也不知道是什么物质
Emits some sort of substance. I'm not sure what it is.
很像白色的火焰 不过一点不热 而是冷的
Like a white flame, but it's not hot, it's cold.
护目镜貌似是用同种材料做的
Glasses look like they're made of the same tech.
护目镜有什么用
What are they for?
白色火焰很刺眼 你会看到的
The glare. You'll see.
还有谁知道你偷了这个
Who else knows you took this?
只有我们
Just us.
不 只有我
No, just me.
不好意思 伙计
Sorry, pal.
来派对的朋友们 谁想来参加智力问答比赛
Party people, who's ready to get their trivia on?
好了 各位 欢迎 我们来了几个新的挑战者
Okay, everybody, welcome. We've got some new challengers.
请热烈欢迎 E=mc大铁锤
Please, welcome E=mc Hammer.
哦 你看 我用这个名儿就是因为E=mc的平方
No, you see, I did it because E=mc squared
正是有名的爱因斯坦动能公式 对吧
is Einstein's formula for kinetic energy, right?
还有 你懂的 能量大到碰都不能碰
And, you know, can't touch this.
好棒啊 巴里
That's great, Barry.
费莉希蒂去哪儿了
So where is Felicity?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
我跟她说了什么时候开始的
I told her it started at...
如果你想买她身上那种连衣裙 千万别省
Feel free to buy yourself that dress.
今晚我穿得太夸张了
I totally overdressed for trivia night.
不 你看起来美极了
No, you look amazing.
是的 美极了
Yeah, you do.
E=mc大铁锤
E=mc hammer.
真有意思
That's funny.
瞧
See?
直到1852年
It wasn't until 1852,
州际铁路在这座欣欣向荣的牛镇
when the transcontinental railroad laid their tracks
铺下第一条轨道
through this thriving cattle town,
我们公司才正式组建
that we became officially incorporated.
同一年 这儿遭遇了一场有史以来最严重的水灾
That same year, the worst flood this area's ever seen hit.
但这场灾难中 诞生了我们中城最伟大的英雄
But from that disaster rose Central City's greatest hero,
农场主 博比·波文·迈克菲里
cattle rancher Bobby Bovine Mcfeely.
博比·迈克菲里 在那场洪水中拯救了17头牛
Bovine Mcfeely saved 17 cows from the great flood.
嘿 小子 口香糖要么
Hey, kid. Gum?
现在 在这次展览会上
And now, for the exhibit
我确定你们会想看看这颗
I'm sure you've all come here to see,
历史上著名的卡恩达克王朝大钻石
the historic Kahndaq dynasty diamond.
小心点 别太靠近
Be careful. Get too close
否则会触发防盗保险系统
and you'll set off the proximity alarms.
我可不想那样
Wouldn't want to do that.
- 三是巴斯德（巴斯德：法国化学家、细菌学家） - 嗯嗯
- Three is Pasteur. - Mm-mm.
三是俄德（DC漫画公司《火星猎人》中的地球人科学家） 四是巴斯德
Three is Erdel, and four is Pasteur.
- 哦对 五呢
- Right. - Five?
- 笛卡尔 - 笛卡尔
- Descartes. - Descartes.
他们确实是在说英语么
Are they even speaking English?
E=mc大铁锤队 得到了这一分
And the points go to E=mc Hammer.
我就知道你们超棒的
I knew you two would make a good team.
那么 费莉希蒂 你是做什么的
So, Felicity, what do you do?
我在做计算机科学方面的工作
I work in computer sciences
- 在奎恩集团 - 是嘛
- at Queen Consolidated. - Really?
你在星城有男朋友么
Do you have a boyfriend in Starling City?
不 不 没有
No, no, there is no one.
我再给你弄点儿饮料
I'll get us some more drinks.
而我喝太多饮料了
And I had too many of those first ones,
我去去就来
so I will be right back.
- 什么 - 老兄啊
- What? - Dude.
老兄 啥
Dude? Wha...
你还要跟我说她对你没意思么
Are you still gonna tell me that she's not into you?
瞧瞧那连衣裙
Look at that dress.
还有当我问起她关于男朋友的问题
And when I asked her the boyfriend question,
她都僵住了
she froze.
是是是 你在这种事儿上还真狡猾
Yeah, you were particularly sly with that one.
费莉希蒂很聪明 乖巧 还很漂亮
Felicity is smart, nice, and pretty.
最重要的是 你交往过的妹子里
And most importantly, she is the first girl
她是第一个真正懂你的
at I have seen you with that really understands
而且她和我一样都认为
and appreciates you for the amazing person
你是多么赞的一个男生
that I am always telling you that you are.
她和你简直是绝配
She's perfect for you,
你还在等什么 巴里
so what are you waiting for, Barry?
它不见了多久了
How long has it been missing?
我不知道
I don't know.
我要再问一遍 思科
I'm gonna ask you again, Cisco.
但我再问的时候
But when I do,
我希望你给我一个比“我不知道”更好的答案
I expect a more specific answer than i don't know.
好了 武器不见了有多久了
Now, how long has this weapon been gone?
一天 也许两天
A day, maybe two.
有个守卫今早没来上班
One of the janitors didn't show up for work this morning.
可能就是他拿走的
He was probably the one who took it.
我没想到
I didn't think that...
你没想到
You didn't think,
因为如果你想到了 你会在造这武器之前
Because if you had, you would have discussed with me
先和我商量一下
first your desire to build something that could,
这东西 理论上可能伤害任何人
in theory, hurt anyone,
特别是 巴里艾伦
and in particular, Barry Allen.
对不起
I'm sorry.
如果你肯听我解释
If you just let me explain...
你知道我是怎么想这些武器的 思科
You know how I feel about weapons, cisco.
他们不属于科技之星实验室
They do not belong in S.T.A.R. Labs.
现在 你要找出那枪在哪里
Now, you are gonna figure out a way to locate this gun,
马上去找
and you are gonna do it right now.
你造的这个 是用来干什么事的
This thing you built, what can it do?
很糟糕的事
Bad stuff.
你说如果有任何可怀疑的事就叫你
You said to call if there was anything suspicious.
这个人参加了两次展览会
This guy went through the tour twice.
没人会那么做
Nobody does that.
这是韦斯特探长
This is Detective West.
我有在博物馆看到伦纳德·斯奈特
I have a visual on Leonard Snart at the museum.
请求立即支援
Requesting immediate back up.
对不起 我以为我知道
I'm sorry. I thought I knew it,
我太兴奋了 我搞砸了
and I got excited, and I... I just hit it.
不 我是说 他们也可能会答错
No, I mean, maybe they'll get it wrong too.
哦 是的 我确定那队
Oh, yeah. I am sure that the team
叫骄傲绝地学徒的
named Pride and Padawans doesn't know the name
不会知道汉索罗的船名
to Han Solo's ship.
哦 亲爱的 你一脸茫然的时候真是可爱
Oh, honey, you are so cute when you're confused.
有人发现斯奈特了
Someone spotted Snart.
- 我要走了 - 我会帮你掩饰的
- I gotta go. - I'll cover for you.
好的 你打算怎么说
All right, what are you gonna say?
我常告诉别人 奥利弗在一家夜总会
I usually tell people Oliver's at a night club with a girl
和一个妹子或者护士喝得烂醉
or nursing a hangover.
没人会相信我会这样的
None of which will work for me.
那说你肚子疼 三餐都拉出来了
Bad stomach ache... Really bad diarrhea.
好吧 我不觉得这是个好借口
Yeah, I'm not comfortable with that excuse.
快走吧
Just go.
注意安全
Stay safe.
我现在在对空气讲话 感觉怪怪的
And I'm talking to air now, which is odd.
而且还根本停不下来
And I'm still doing it.
斯奈特
Snart!
- 没事吧 - 啊 辣辣得疼
- You okay? - Ahh, aah, it burns.
跑步测试时间
Time for a test run.
让我们看看你有多快
Let's see how fast you are.
啊
Gah!
不
No!
No.
还是感觉麻麻的
It's still numb.
表现出第三度冻伤的状态
It's presenting itself like third degree frostbite.
我以为他会迅速恢复
I thought he had hyper healing.
恢复速度也被减缓了
It's been slowed.
如果你的细胞再生速度没有那么快
If your cells weren't regenerating at the rate
那你的血管会冻成冰块
they are, your blood vessels would have frozen solid
这对神经的损害将是永久的
and the nerve damage would have been permanent.
你该庆幸你还活着
You're lucky to be alive.
斯奈特并不是变异人
Snart wasn't another meta-human.
他有把枪
He has some kind of gun.
会把东西冻住 会让我速度变慢
It froze things, slowed me down...
慢到我没时间去救别人
Enough that I wasn't in time to save someone.
根据他的履历记录
According to his record,
斯奈特甚至没有念完高中
Snart didn't even bother to finish high school,
那他是怎么造出这把高科技冷冻枪的
so how did he build a handheld high tech snow machine?
科技之星实验室制造了这把冷冻枪
S.T.A.R. Labs built the cold gun.
威尔斯博士和凯特林与此事无关
Dr. Wells and Caitlin had nothing to do with this.
是我造的这把枪
I built the gun.
你造的
You did?
为什么
Why?
因为速度和冰冷是相互对立的
Because speed and cold are opposites.
温度是由原子的震荡速度
Temperature is measured
来衡量的
by how quickly the atoms of something are oscillating.
振荡得越快 就会越热
The faster they are, the hotter it is,
当物体冰冷的时候，从原子的角度来讲，他们变慢了
and when things are cold, they're slower on the atomic level.
当分子完全静止下来时 就叫做
When there's no movement at all, it's called...
绝对零度
Absolute zero.
对
Yeah.
我设计了一个制造绝对零度的简易制冷器
I designed a compact cryo engine to achieve absolute zero.
我制造它是为了阻止你
I built it to stop you.
我那时根本不知道你是谁 巴里
I didn't know who you were then, Barry.
我是说 要是你变成了像是马顿或是尼比斯
I mean, what if you turned out to be some psycho,
那样的变态呢
like Mardon or Nimbus?
但我没有 不是吗
But I didn't. Did I?
我们建立这整个组织是为了让你可以去做好事
We built the entire structure you're standing in to do good,
但是它却被炸飞了
and it blew up.
考虑到这一点 你应该理解为什么思科
In the wake of that, you can understand why Cisco
会想要做最坏的准备
would want to be prepared for the worst.
我明白那个 但我不明白的是
I can understand that, but what I can't understand
你们为什么不告诉我你们都做了什么
is why you didn't tell me what you did.
我是说 在我们共同经历过这么多之后
I mean, after all we've been through,
我以为你们信任我
I thought you trusted me.
-我以为我们是朋友 -我们是的 巴里
- I thought we were friends. - We are, Barry.
你过你能早些告诉我
I mean, if you would have just told me,
我就可以有所准备
I could have been prepared.
但是你没有 今晚就有人死了
But instead, someone died tonight.
我必须背负那些责任
And I have to live with that.
不 思科 我们都要
No, Cisco. We all do.
观众们在从今夜市中剧院
Theatergoers remain shaken
残忍诡异的攻击事件中幸存下来之后
after surviving tonight's brutal and bizarre attack
依旧惊魂未定
in a downtown theater...
新闻说 你还好吗
The news... Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
这件事还要持续多久
How long is this gonna go on?
看来要开始冷战了
Seems like the cold treatment is going around.
现在不是时候 艾瑞斯 拜托了
Not now, Iris, please.
不 就是现在
Yes, now.
你现在和我当初想报名警察学院
You did the same thing when I tried to sign up
却没告诉你的时候一模一样
for the police academy without telling you.
你好几周都没和我说话
You didn't speak to me for weeks...
直到我撤回了我的申请
Not until I withdrew my application.
但是 爸爸 我这次不会再让步了
Well, I am not withdrawing this time, dad.
不管你喜不喜欢 我都要和埃迪交往
I am dating Eddie whether you like it or not.
-埃迪是我的搭档 -我知道
- Eddie's my partner. - I know.
不 你不懂 你不是警察
But you don't. You're not a cop.
你不明白搭档意味着什么
You don't know what having a partner means.
我去哪 他就去哪
Wherever I go, he goes,
而我去的地方不一定安全 艾瑞斯
and where I go isn't always safe, Iris.
我需要百分百的集中精神
I need to be 100% focused.
现在 我没办法完全集中
Now, there's a part of me that isn't focused,
因为我没把艾迪看作是我的搭档
that doesn't see Eddie as my partner,
而看作是你的男朋友
but as your boyfriend.
所以如果他受伤了或者是遭遇了更严重的事
So if he gets hurt or worse,
而我就在场
and I'm there,
我要怎么面对你
how am I gonna look at you?
你又将如何看待我
How you gonna look at me?
现在 我不是对你生气
Now, I'm not mad at you,
但这就是为什么这件事对我来说
but that's why this is
那么艰难的原因 你明白吗
so hard for me. Do you understand?
我们今晚回去
We're going back tonight.
-回哪去 -博物馆
- Back where? - To the museum.
那颗钻石可不会自己跑到我们手里来
That diamond isn't going to steal itself.
超级枪把你的脑子冻住了吗 史纳特
Super gun freeze your brain, Snart?
博物馆现在到处是警察的
The museum's gonna be crawling with police by now,
-还有那道红色印迹 -这能阻止那道印迹
- and The Streak. - This can stop The Streak.
这能伤到他 并且我知道他真正的弱点
It hurts him, and I know his real weakness.
所以我们现在就走 除非你想退出
So we go, unless you want out.
我们都想退出 活着退出
We both want out... Alive.
所以你俩早就想过 计划好了
So you thought ahead and made a plan.
至少我还教会了你点东西
Least I taught you something.
那你还在等什么呢
So what are you waiting for?
开枪啊
Shoot me.
你最好现在就开枪射我
You better put a bullet in my brain right now,
因为如果你不这么做
because if you don't,
如果我再看到你们
if I ever see either one of you again...
你根本不懂 是不是
You don't get it, do you?
那团红影就在外边
This blur is out there,
中城不再是你的游乐园了
and Central City ain't your playground anymore.
不 它是
Sure, it is.
巴里
Barry?
Barry.
什么 你在干什么
What? What are you doing?
你该回你的酒店
You should go back to your hotel.
-睡觉了 -你也是
- Get some sleep. - You should too.
不是说回我的酒店 我是说睡觉
Not go back to my hotel... I meant get some sleep.
不行
I can't.
每次我闭上眼睛 就会看见那个人的脸
Every time I close my eyes, I see that man's face.
我看着他死去
I watched him die.
我必须得跑更快
I have to go faster.
巴里 那不是你的错
Barry, it's not your fault.
这也不是思科的错
And it's not Cisco's, either.
巴里 我知道你很沮丧
Barry, I know you're upset,
但你得从他的角度去看待这件事情
but you have to look at this from his point of view.
不 我知道的
No, I get it.
他不相信我
He didn't trust me.
巴里 你遇到我们的时候 我 奥利弗 和狄格
Barry, when you met us... Me, Oliver, and Dig...
我们就想上好油的射箭机那样默契
We were this well-oiled archery machine.
但一开始并不是那样
But it didn't start out that way.
而且不像你们这些家伙 我们没有一整夜待在一起
And unlike you guys, we weren't tossed together overnight.
我们一段时间才集合一次
We came together one at a time.
相信我 要相信奥利佛
Believe me, it took much more than watching Oliver
比看着他做三文鱼梯难多了
do the salmon ladder to make me trust him.
我亲眼见过这样的生活会对人们有什么影响
I've seen firsthand what this life can do to people.
这本来就是条孤独的路
It's a lonely path.
不要再让自己陷入更无畏的孤寂中了
Don't make it any lonelier than it has to be.
不许动
Freeze!
你想像这扇门一样吗
You want to end up like that door?
嗨 亲爱的
Hi there.
我想出了一个办法追踪冰冻队长
I figured out a way to track Captain Cold.
你别再给这些家伙起名了
You gotta stop naming these guys.
-巴里 听听他说 -怎样做
- Barry, listen to him. - How?
这个冷冻枪是由一个引擎控制单元供能的
The cold gun is powered by an engine control unit,
一台微型处理机控制空气转为燃料的比率
a microcomputer that regulates air-to-fuel ratios
那样内膛中备用的冷冻液体就
so the sub-cooled fluid
不会溢出也不会
in the chambers don't overflow and...
-爆炸 -对
- Explode. - Right.
这个微机控制单元可以无线接收我平板上的更新信息
This E.C.U. Was receiving updates wirelessly from my tablet.
如果我用中诚的网络增加信号
If I boost the signal using Central City's network
然后发送错误更新信息
and send a false update,
我们就会收到回响信号 然后
we'll get a ping back, and then...
我们就能找到史纳特了
We can locate Snart.
这要花多长时间
How long will it take?
首先我得先黑进中城的网络系统
First I have to hack into the City's network,
所以我也不清楚 可能30分钟吧
so I don't know, 30 minutes, maybe?
我能在一分钟之内搞定
I can do it in less than one.
论黑客技术 我可是当今世上最快的女人了
When it comes to hacking, I'm the fastest woman alive.
哦 没我想象的那么厉害啊
Ow! That was not as badass as I pictured.
行了 我进去了
All right, I'm in.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding?
好吧 我在发送更新信息了
All right, I'm sending the updates.
连上了
We're connected.
网络进行三角定位
Network is triangulating the location.
找到他了 他在纳尔逊街 往西走
We got him. He's heading west on Nelson
朝火车站前进
toward the train station.
如果他要走了 就说明史纳特先生已经得到
If he's leaving, it appears Mr. Snart may have gotten
他想要的东西了
what he came for.
当我们都专心一致的时候
When we put our minds to it,
老兄 没什么可以阻挡我们
dude, nothing can stop us.
哦 你把你的耳机关掉了
Oh, you turned your ear piece off.
那我们要怎么对话
How are we gonna talk to each other?
我现在不是很想说话
I don't feel like talking right now.
所有单位注意
All available units,
有人发现嫌犯在中城火车站出没
suspect spotted at Central City train station.
我们找到史纳特了
We got Snart.
-在这等增援 -等增援 没门
- Wait here for back up. - Wait for back up? No way.
那是命令
That's an order.
-你们应该跟着巴里 -你听见他说的了 菲莉西蒂
- You should go after Barry. - You heard him, Felicity.
他想一个人干
He wants to do this alone.
当然了 他肯定那么说
Of course, he said that.
他很受伤
He's hurt.
你们是他的团队 是他的朋友
You're his team and his friends.
如果每次绿箭侠叫我后退时 我都能获得五分钱的话
If I had a nickel for every time The Arrow told me to back off,
那我估计跟奥利弗·奎恩一样有钱了
I would be as rich as Oliver Queen,
我之所以提到他是因为他是我所知道的最有钱的人
who I mention because he's the richest person I know,
或曾经是
or used to be.
我想说的是
The point is,
你要支持你的搭档
you have your partner's back
无论发生什么事情
no matter what.
我有些东西也许能帮上忙
I have something that might help.
我是你的搭档 不是你的助手
I'm your partner, not your assistant.
你跑不了了
There's nowhere to run.
我以前没见过你
I didn't see you before.
你的妈妈知道你已经过了宵禁时间了吗
Your mom know you're out past your bedtime?
如果你想逃走 你应该搭上比火车还快
If you wanted to get away you should've taken something
的交通工具
faster than a train.
如果我不打算逃走呢
That's if I wanted to get away.
我在运钞车那里见到了你的弱点
I've seen your weakness at the armored car,
然后是在剧院
then at the theater.
你瞧 当你正忙着拯救世界的时候
See, while you're busy saving everybody,
我在拯救我自己
I'll be saving myself.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
啊
Ahh!
挺不错的嘛 小子
Pretty fast, kid,
但还是不够快
but not fast enough.
谢谢你
Thank you.
为什么
For what?
你逼我升级了我的游戏
You forced me to up my game,
不只是这把枪
not only with this gun,
还有我怎么看这份工作
but with how I think about the job.
很有教育意义
It's been educational.
放下武器
Drop it.
这是一把原型冷冻枪
This is a prototype cold gun,
四倍的尺寸 四倍的能量
four times the size, four times the power.
我还在疑惑你在和谁讲话
I was wondering who you were talking to.
嘿 除非你想自食其果
Hey, unless you want a taste of your own medicine,
我就让你尝尝
I'd back the hell up.
你的手在抖
Your hands are shaking.
你还没杀过人
You've never killed anyone.
凡是都有第一次 冷冻队长
There's a first time for everything, Captain Cold.
我会杀了你
I will shoot you.
你赢了 孩子
You win, kid.
后会有期
I'll see you around.
嘿 把钻石留下
Hey, leave the diamond.
别得寸进尺了
Don't push your luck.
就算我想 也杀不了他
Couldn't shoot him if I wanted to.
这其实是科技之星实验室的吸尘器
This is actually the S.T.A.R. Labs vacuum cleaner
只是上面有很多LED灯
with a lot of L.E.D's.
让我们帮你暖和暖和
Let's get you warm.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们一直在追踪史纳特
We've been trying to track Snart,
但他肯定是切断了信号
but he must have disconnected the signal somehow.
我们会找到他的 思科 一起携手
We'll find him, Cisco, together.
你有一个很棒的团队 巴里
You have a great team here, Barry.
说起团队 我也许该回到我自己的团队了
Speaking of teams, I should probably get back to mine.
很高兴见到你 斯莫克小姐
It was nice meeting you, Ms. Smoak.
麻烦代我们向绿箭侠问好
Please extend a hello to The Arrow for us.
我会的
I will.
再见 菲莉西蒂
Good-bye, Felicity.
拜拜 巴里
Bye, Barry.
真是一位卓越的年轻女性
Remarkable young woman.
她很特别
She's special.
是啊
Yeah, she is.
思科
Cisco,
别再那么做了
don't you ever do anything like that again.
听明白没有
Do you understand me?
听明白了
Yes, sir.
-嘿 爸爸 -嘿
- Hey, dad. - Hey.
如果你是来找埃迪的话 他在物证处
If you're looking for Eddie, he's in evidence.
我是来找你的
I am looking for you.
我是来再次和你道歉的
I came to apologize... Again.
你是真的想要碰碰运气吗
You're really trying to hit that magic number, aren't you?
听我说 爸爸 我只想让你知道
Look, dad, I just want you to know
无论你做了什么事
that there is nothing that you could do
都不会改变你在我心目中的形象
that would ever change the way that I look at you.
而且我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
我应该要考虑到我和埃迪在一起
I should have thought about how
对你带来的影响
it would affect you if Eddie and I...
听着
Listen...
今晚追踪这个史纳特时
Chasing down this Snart character tonight?
他让我开窍了
He had the draw on me.
埃迪救了我一命
Eddie saved my life.
也许是我低估了他
Maybe I underestimated him.
从现在起 再也没有秘密了
From now on, no more secrets.
再也没有秘密
No more secrets.
-好了 去看埃迪吧 -好的
- Well, go see Eddie. - Okay.
感谢他照顾好你的老爸
Thank him for watching out for your old man.
红色踪迹
搭救火车乘客
我刚才尖叫了吗
Did I just yelp?
-是的 -我尖叫了
- Yeah. - I yelped.
对不起 我不是想要吓着你
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
不要告诉我你是来这救我的
Don't tell me you're here to save me.
搭火车还是最安全的旅行方法
Taking the train is still one of the safest ways to travel.
我还以为是飞机
I thought that was airplanes.
额
Mm...
你记得你告诉过我一段经历吗
You remember when you told me you had a little experience
喜欢一个以不同的方式看待你的人
liking somebody who didn't see you the same way?
那个人是艾瑞斯 对吗
That was Iris, right?
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
从小细节里看出来的
It's the little things.
她看着别处时你盯着她的眼神
The way you linger on her when she isn't looking,
你勉强装出的笑容
the smile you fake to play the part,
静静地坚守着自己的梦想
quiet dreams you keep to yourself.
就像你和奥利弗
Like you and Oliver.
有经历过才会知道啊
Takes one to know one.
我怕这会改变所有事情
I'm afraid it'll change everything.
它会
It will,
但也许也不是坏事
but maybe that's not such a bad thing.
我们到底怎么了
What is wrong with us?
我们都那么适合对方
We are perfectly perfect for each other.
却坐在这里 为了我们得不到的人而伤感
Yet we're sitting here, pining for people we can't have.
我想他们说的是对的
I guess what they say is true.
得不到的永远在骚动
Opposites do attract.
如果你需要什么 我会一瞬间冲过去
If you ever need anything, I will race over in a heartbeat.
我也是
Same.
最大马力冲过去
Well, as fast I can run,
可能得久一点 但我还是会来的
which might take me a while, but I will still come.
拜拜 菲莉西蒂
Bye, Felicity.
拜拜 巴里
Bye, Barry.
呜呼
Whoo-hoo!
我知道我们好一阵子没开工了
I know it's been a while since we pulled that job.
我知道那进行得不太顺利
I know it didn't go so well for you,
我也知道我说过我们的合作结束了
and I know I said we were finished.
但事情变了
But things have changed.
如果我还想在中城做事
If I want to keep working in Central City,
我需要一个新伙伴
I'm gonna need a new kind of crew.
我要找一个像你一样的人
I'm gonna need someone like you.
你能忍受极端分子
You're tolerant of extremes.
你有一定的技巧
You have certain skills.
你只是需要一些方向
You just need some direction.
而我能帮你指明
And I can give that to you.
你还喜欢冒险玩火吗
You still like playing with fire?
那你会爱上这个的
You're gonna love this.
那么
So...
来吗 米克 还是要退出
Are you in Mick? Or are you out?
兄弟 我当然来
Yeah buddy, I'm in.